gotfound.ca 2014-06-19

# Online Privacy Policy | Search Engine People Blog

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as text you type in this website. This site does not use ClickTale to collect any personally identifiable information entered in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see [Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx). We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to improve service.  
You can choose to disable the Service at [http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html](http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html)

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).

\- To send periodic emails.

\- The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

\- Anonymous aggregate information from visitors of our site such as the time of visit, pages visited, and the IP address of your computer may be used for analytics purposes.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Your information can be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do use cookies on our site. Cookies are small pieces of information that some websites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other sites, searchenginepeople.com and other third party services or partners on our site may use cookies to identify visitors. To learn more, consult the privacy policies of our third party partners. Most browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:

Search Engine People Inc.  
1305 Pickering Parkway, Suite 500  
Pickering, Ontario  
L1V 3P2  
contact@searchenginepeople.com  
905-421-9340
